Muhammad Hassan Tariq

Full Stack Developer



Personal details

Muhammad Hassan Tariq



hkhankor@gmail.com



+92 346 9413675



Thana malakand agency KPK, 23000 Malakand



February 6th, 2002



Thana malakand agency KPK,



Pakistani



hasankhankor.github.io/Portfolio _gh_pages

Skills

WordPress 0000 Web Development



Android Development



Languages

Urdu **English**

Hobbies

Pashto

Indoor Games

Education

ICS Lamps College Peshawar, Peshawar

Obtained Marks 52%

BS in Software Engineering

Abasyn University Islamabad, Islamabad

C.GPA is 2.76

Employment

Freelancing, Islambad

Web Developer

May 2021 - Present

Apr 2017 - Jun 2019

Sep 2019 - Present

Design, develop and deliver Web apps to clients according to their specifications

Profile

I am a Full Stack Developer I have an experience of 1 years. i can accommodate you in less time from the market and i can help you in designing your business, special events. I will design Websites and Webapps Front-end and Back-end using Php, Node JS, SQL, NOSQL, React. is and I will design Mobile Apps Frontend and Back-end using Andoid Studio and Frameworks I will work as Requirment Engineer.

Certificates

National Imitative for Artificial Intelligence & security

Present

References

References available upon request.

Achievements

Vice President of Karwan-e-Pakistan of Abasyn University Of islamabad